IBRAHEM RAMADAN EL-SAYED ALI

Dot Net Developer

Mobile: (022) 01098738718

Email: ibrahem.ramadan@cis.asu.edu.eg

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ibrahem-ramadan

Github: github.com/lbrahem-Ramadan

Facebook: <u>facebook.com/ibrahem.ramadan.12</u>

Address: Cairo ,Egypt

PERSONAL INFO

- Military Service : Completed.

- Marial Status: Single.

- Age: 24 Year.

Nationality: Egyptian.

- Languages: Arabic [Native], English [Very Good].

- Hobbies: Football, Running.

SUMMARY

Professional Software Developer with +1 year of Experience in Software Development including Web Development and Desktop Application Development. Passionate about Developing User-Friendly Software Applications. Excellent Problem-Solving Skills and Ability to Perform well in a Team. Seeking to help my Organization to Develop their Product as a Software Engineer, as well as Grow and Develop my Own Skills as a Coder.

EXPERIENCE

Software Quality Control Training

Telecom Egypt Academy (WE) Aug 2018 - Oct 2018

Android Basics Internship

FCAI Benha University Aug 2017 - Sep 2017

DNS Operation and DNSSEC Workshop

DNS Enterpreneurship Center

MSP Tech Club - FCIS/ASU

Technical Member 2016 - 2017

EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree of Computer Science

Ain Shams University 2015 - 2019

ન્દ્ર TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages

- ASP.Net [Intermediate]

- C# [Intermediate] - C/C++ [Intermediate]

[Intermediate] - Java

- Python [Beginner]

Markup Languages

[Intermediate] - JavaScript [Intermediate] - CSS [Intermediate]

- Bootstrap [Intermediate]

Concepts

- Object Oriented Programming

- Data Structures

- Algorithms

- Image Processing

- Parallel Programming.

Database

- Oracle Database

- MySQL

Testing Skills

- Manual Testing (Unit Testing - Integration Testing)

Version Control Systems

- Git and GitHub.

SOFT SKILLS

Team Worker

Good Communication Skills

Time Management and Organization

Efficient Note-Taker

Ability to Learn New Technologies

Environment Adaptability

Self-Learning

Researching Skills

PROJECTS

Railway Reservation System SQL Database Using ADO.net

Travel Agency System
Data Structure Using C++

Music Sorter Windows App Using C#

MIPS Processor
Using VHDL

Blood Donation Application
Mobile App Using Android

Using Assembly Language

■ Image Encryption System Windows App Using C#

Chat System Windows App Using C#

Online Shopping System
 Oracle DB Using ODB.net

FOS Operating System cmd App Using C